<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
~  Copyright (c) 2018, WSO2 Inc. (http://wso2.com) All Rights Reserved.
~
~  WSO2 Inc. licenses this file to you under the Apache License,
~  Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except
~  in compliance with the License.
~  You may obtain a copy of the License at
~
~   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
~
~  Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing,
~  software distributed under the License is distributed on an
~  "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY
~  KIND, either express or implied.  See the License for the
~  specific language governing permissions and limitations
~  under the License.
-->
<component name="cerner-search" type="synapse/template">
    <subComponents>
        <component name="searchById">
            <file>searchById.xml</file>
            <description>Search a specific Resource By ID.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchPatient">
            <file>searchPatient.xml</file>
            <description>The Patient resource provides general demographic information about a person receiving health care services from a specific organization.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchRelatedPerson">
            <file>searchRelatedPerson.xml</file>
            <description>The RelatedPerson resource provides information about a person who is involved in the care of a patient but has no formal responsibility.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchImmunization">
            <file>searchImmunization.xml</file>
            <description>The Immunization resource includes the view of current and historical administration of vaccinations to a patient in all health care settings</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchMedicationAdministration">
            <file>searchMedicationAdministration.xml</file>
            <description>The Medication Administration resource provides information about medications and vaccines administered to a patient or consumed by a patient</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchMedicationStatement">
            <file>searchMedicationStatement.xml</file>
            <description>The Medication Statement resource provides a snapshot in time of known medications taken by the patient now or in the past reported by either the patient, significant other or a provider.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchMedicationOrder">
            <file>searchMedicationOrder.xml</file>
            <description>The Medication Order resource provides orders for all medications along with administration instructions for a patient in both the inpatient and outpatient setting</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchCarePlan">
            <file>searchCarePlan.xml</file>
            <description>The CarePlan resource describes the intentions of how one or more practitioners plan to deliver care to a specific patient.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchGoal">
            <file>searchGoal.xml</file>
            <description>The Goal resource describes intended objectives for a patient.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchAllergyIntolerance">
            <file>searchAllergyIntolerance.xml</file>
            <description>The AllergyIntolerance resource provides the clinical assessment of a patient’s allergy or intolerance</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchCondition">
            <file>searchCondition.xml</file>
            <description>The Condition resource is used to record details about a patient’s problems, diagnoses, or other health matters that are concerning.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchProcedure">
            <file>searchProcedure.xml</file>
            <description>The Procedure resource returns current and historical procedures performed on a patient.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchDiagnosticReport">
            <file>searchDiagnosticReport.xml</file>
            <description>The DiagnosticReport resource typically provides a textual set of information and interpretation after performing a diagnostic service or procedure</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchObservation">
            <file>searchObservation.xml</file>
            <description>The Observation resource provides measurements or simple assertions about a patient.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchSchedule">
            <file>searchSchedule.xml</file>
            <description>The Schedule resource provides a time period (planning horizon) where time slots are defined for booking an appointment.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchSlot">
            <file>searchSlot.xml</file>
            <description>The Slot resource returns time slots from a schedule which are available for booking an appointment..</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchAppointment">
            <file>searchAppointment.xml</file>
            <description>The Appointment resource provides information about scheduled appointments </description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchDevice">
            <file>searchDevice.xml</file>
            <description>The Device resource currently exposes the known implant history for a patient at this site. </description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchNewEncounter">
            <file>searchNewEncounter.xml</file>
            <description>The Encounter resource provides admissions or visits during which health care services were provided to a patient </description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchPerson">
            <file>searchPerson.xml</file>
            <description>The Person resource identifies an individual outside of a specific health care context providing a mechanism to link person resources across different facilities or organizations </description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchContract">
            <file>searchContract.xml</file>
            <description>The Contract resource is currently limited to representing people who are authorized to view a patient’s data </description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchBinary">
            <file>searchBinary.xml</file>
            <description>The Binary resource can contain any clinical content such as text, images, and PDFs.  This resource is currently limited to Continuity of Care Documents (CCD), clinical documents, and diagnostic reports.</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchDocumentReference">
            <file>searchDocumentReference.xml</file>
            <description>The DocumentReference resource is used to reference a clinical document for a patient within the health system</description>
        </component>
        <component name="searchPractitioner">
            <file>searchPractitioner.xml</file>
            <description>The Practitioner resource provides information about a person formally involved in the care of a patient on behalf of a healthcare facility.</description>
        </component>

    </subComponents>
</component>